<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogposts on Simon Says!</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogposts on Simon Says!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Website</title>
      <link>/post/2019/06/08/operating-a-website-under-gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/06/08/operating-a-website-under-gdpr/</guid>
      <description>When I decided to have a website that keeps a record of some of the things I am interested in, it was quickly apparent to me that there were many design choices to be made. Of course, having a multitude of options almost certainly means the end-product could differ enormously, not just visual but also under the hood.
Since I will (probably!) be the only one writing for this website, I decided I do not need a fancy content management system with a fancy online collaborative writing tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mistaken Rules</title>
      <link>/post/2019/05/04/mistaken-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/05/04/mistaken-rules/</guid>
      <description>Recently I learnt that a regulation I would have welcomed as an undergraduate at the University of Mannheim actually exists at the University of Cologne. In Cologne, coursework that is completed during a semester abroad can be counted toward the degree albeit on a pass-fail basis rather than graded. This, presumably, levels the playing field between different partner (or even non-partner) institutions with regard to academic rigor and grading cultures. I would have welcomed such a rule as an undergraduate as I had a hard time reconciling these vast differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG
Simon Christian Schulten Gumbertstraße 186 40229 Düsseldorf
Kontakt: E-Mail: Simon[Unterstrich]Schulten[ät]web[Punkt]de
Verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs. 2 RStV: Simon Christian Schulten Gumbertstraße 186 40229 Düsseldorf
Haftungsausschluss:
Haftung für Inhalte
Die Inhalte unserer Seiten wurden mit größter Sorgfalt erstellt. Für die Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit und Aktualität der Inhalte können wir jedoch keine Gewähr übernehmen. Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs. 2 RStV:
Simon Christian Schulten
Kontakt
Haftungsausschluss:
Haftung für Inhalte
Die Inhalte unserer Seiten wurden mit größter Sorgfalt erstellt. Für die Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit und Aktualität der Inhalte können wir jedoch keine Gewähr übernehmen. Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich. Nach §§ 8 bis 10 TMG sind wir als Diensteanbieter jedoch nicht verpflichtet, übermittelte oder gespeicherte fremde Informationen zu überwachen oder nach Umständen zu forschen, die auf eine rechtswidrige Tätigkeit hinweisen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inaugural Blog Post</title>
      <link>/post/2019/02/05/inaugural-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/02/05/inaugural-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why should a PhD student write a blog?&amp;rdquo;, you might ask. Do PhD students not have enough on their plate with study and research alone? Who reads these obscure blogs, anyways? It seems futile.
I think these are legitimite concerns and yet I have just started a blog. So let me address these questions in my first posting, if anything to set some goals for my attempt at blogging.
It is true, my day is full enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Simon Schulten and I am a first-year PhD student at DICE where I study economics and hope to work on topics related to market design and behavioural economics. I also hope to produce some blog posts on topics of interest to me (and hopefully you!).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>